Even though the focus of this part of the course is on designing
虽然这部分的重点是设计实验
experiments to measure the effect of changes and manipulations,
并衡量变化和操控措施的效果
it's worth noting that it's useful to conduct dummy tests in certain cases.
但是值得注意的是 在某些情形下 可以开展虚拟测试
A dummy test is one that implements no changes
虚拟测试是指不进行任何更改
and just compares two equivalent groups with one another.
只是比较两个对等的小组
For the AB testing paradigm,
与 A/B 测试对应的话
a dummy test is also called an AA test.
虚拟测试也称为 A/A 测试
If a dummy test is a comparison between equivalent groups,
如果虚拟测试只是比较两个对等的组
then why would we want to do this?
那么为何还要比较呢？
There are two major reasons.
原因主要有两个
First of all you can use a dummy test to make
首先 虚拟测试可以验证
sure that your experiment is working as expected.
实验是否达到预期
You can check that each of your groups is receiving an equal number of participants,
你可以检查每组是否分配了相同数量的参与者
and that the outcomes of your invariant and evaluation
并检查不变指标和评估指标的结果
metrics both conform to the expectation of seeing no change.
是否都像期望的那样没有变化
If any of these things don't come out as expected,
如果有任何不符合预期的地方
then you should check for problems such as in the engineering side of the design.
那么你应该检查设计是否有问题 例如工程问题
It's important to note that there's always the chance of making a type one error.
务必注意 始终有可能出现 I 型错误
So, a statistical significance on a single metric may not necessarily be a deal breaker,
所以单个指标的统计显著性不一定起到决定性作用
just something to investigate.
只是要调查的一个方面
The second big reason why you might want to run a dummy test is if you need to collect
运行虚拟测试的另一个主要原因是
information about the behavior of your metrics in order to scope out the full design.
需要收集指标行为信息 从而获得完整的设计
If you don't have reliable historic data
如果没有可靠的历史数据
to predict the distribution of the outcome metrics,
来预测输出指标的分布情况
a dummy test can give you some insight into
那么虚拟测试可以告诉我们
how much variability and experimental result with no effect would look like.
没有效果的实验结果变化性如何
Baseline rates obtained from a dummy test can also help out in
通过虚拟测试得出的基准比率
figuring out how large an experiment needs to be and how long it needs to run.
还有助于我们确定实验应该多大 需要运行多长时间
Of course, a dummy test is not without its downsides.
当然 虚拟测试也存在缺点
Time spent running a dummy test is time that you're not using to run your actual test.
如果花时间运行虚拟测试 就没有时间运行实际测试了
Since timeliness of results is an important virtue of experiment design,
对于实验设计来说 结果的时效性很重要
running a dummy test may not be reasonable
所以可能没必要运行虚拟测试
except for companies with the largest user basis.
除非企业拥有庞大的用户群
It might be the case that you'll need to go
有时候 你需要直接运行实验
ahead with the experiment without a dummy test for
而不运行虚拟测试来验证实验
verification and just keep an eye out for any major deviations from your expectations.
并留意是否存在偏离预期的重大情形